##### Privacy policy of VPNArea (Offshore Security LTD)

This policy has been modified on 28 Jan 2021 to reflect the replacement of BitPay with Coinbase as payment method for cryptocurrencies.  
  
**Information We Collect**  
  
You do not have to give us any personally identifiable ("personal") information to browse our Site, but to subscribe to our Services you must create an account and register with us. We do not track you or your internet activities while connected to the VPN Service or VPN Servers.  
  
We collect the following information from registered users:  
\- Account Information. To create an account, you will need to provide with the following personal information: email address.  
  
\- We don’t verify your email address so you have our permission to supply us with non-existing email address. If you do provide us with an email address, real or not, we will store it in a secure way in line with industry standards. We will treat it as personal information and will protect it in line with our privacy policy.  
  
\- You will have to provide us with an username and password in order to register an account with us.  
\- For VAT calculation purposes EU visitors, must select a country for the account. The country choice is not validated by us and it does not have any bearing on your account, it is purely for the purpose of calculate VAT tax if such applies to your purchase.  
\- In order to be able to process refunds for PayPal, Paymentwall and Coinbase we will collect a transaction ID. If you wish that information to be deleted please refer to “Right to be forgotten” or “How To Modify Your Personal Information” sections below.  
\- If you purchase "Dedicated IP" add-on we will keep a record of which username purchased which dedicated IP. As a dedicated IP owner you can request we remove this information. We also remove Dedicated IP ownership information if we re-assign the dedicated IP to another customer if you let it expire.  
  
**Payments**  
To register an account with us you will have to place a payment which will be processed by one of the following payment processors externally - PayPal.com, Paymentwall.com, Coinbase.com.  
  
[All PayPal transactions are subject to the PayPal Privacy Policy.](#)  
  
Please refer to their privacy policies if you agree to pay via any of them.  
  
**No Logs**  
  
We do not monitor, record or store logs for any single customer's VPN activity. We do not monitor, record or store any login dates, timestamps, incoming and outgoing IP addresses, bandwidth statistics or any other identifiable data of any VPN users using our VPN servers. We do not log or track any DNS requests sent to our DNS servers.  
  
**Site Visitors**  
  
We collect certain information automatically from visitors to our Site via Cookies. For more information refer to our official Cookie Policy here: [Cookie Policy](https://vpnarea.com/front/home/cookie). We do not track user activities outside of our Site, nor do we track the browsing activities of users who are logged into our VPN service via cookies or in any other way.  
  
**How We Use Your Information**  
  
The information we collect through our Site and Services is primarily used to create new accounts, collect payment for our Services, identify and communicate with current subscribers, or offer troubleshooting or customer support. We may also use personal information for the following reasons:  
  
To verify your identity when you login to the Site or Service; For internal record keeping; To complete your online order; To administer and improve our Site and Services; To target our Site content to your preferences; To respond to your requests or inquires and for other customer service purposes; To notify you of changes to the service; To analyze usage and trends on our Site and to better understand how users use the Site and Services.  

**Disclosure of Your Information To others**  
We do not sell or disclose your personal data to others. We cannot provide information that we do not have.  
  
Offshore Security EOOD (VPNArea) aims to protect privacy and the privacy rights of our customers. Although we will comply with all valid court orders in our jurisdiction, our lawyers will inspect every legal request for compliance with the law. Whenever possible we will provide the customer with an opportunity to object to any requested disclosures. Offshore Security EOOD (VPNArea) will not comply with any request that require only good will or does not involve court-order.  
  
There haven't at any point been any such requests in our company yet.  
  
**Cookies**  
Please refer to our official Cookie Policy here: [Cookie Policy](https://vpnarea.com/front/home/cookie)  
  
**The Security Measures We Have In Place**  
  
We use security measures that are consistent with industry standards to protect your personal information from loss, theft, misuse or unauthorized access or disclosure or destruction,. All employees are kept up-to-date on our security and privacy practices. In addition, access to user or subscriber personal information is restricted to those who need to know such information to perform their job functions. Where appropriate, we use encryption, firewalls, access controls, passwords, and/or physical security measures to protect the personal information we collect and maintain about you against unauthorized access and disclosure. Our databases and emails are hosted in data centers which offer state of the art physical security. Where any user data is concerned we use encryption in line with industry standards or better.  
  
**Links To Other Sites**  
  
We provide links to third party websites as a convenience to our users. These links are not intended as an endorsement of or referral to the linked websites. We recommend that you carefully read the privacy statements, notices and terms of use or service of any other websites that you visit. We do not have any control over such websites, and therefore we assume no responsibility for the manner in which the organizations that operate such websites collect, use, maintain or disclose your personal information.  
  
**Marketing Emails**  
  
We do not send any marketing e-mails to our users. The communication you receive from us is only to provide the service as needed.  
  
**How To Modify Your Personal Information** Requests to review or amend your account information beyond the scope offered in Members Area, or for technical support, service information, and changes in usage should be sent to: support \[at\] vpnarea.com.  
  
We try to respond to all requests in a timely manner.  
  
**Your right to obtaining a registry extract**  
You have a right to receive a listing of any actively provided information, if any, that we have stored under your account. If you would to make use of the aforementioned right, please contact support \[at\] vpnarea.com for more information.  
  
**Your right to be forgotten**  
Under GDPR you have the right to be forgotten. We absolutely agree and we will be happy to delete any information we have about you.  
  
If you would like to exercise this right please contact support \[at\] vpnarea.com with the email address associated with your account and we will delete any such information.  
  
**Minors and Children's Privacy**  
  
Our Site and Services are not intended for anyone under the age of 18. If you are a parent or guardian and believe that your child under 13 has provided personal information to us, please contact us so that we can delete the child's information.  
  
**International Users**  
Offshore Security EOOD (VPNArea) computer systems are physically based in Switzerland, so your personal information will be processed by us in Switzerland, where data protection and privacy regulations may be different than in other parts of the world. When you create an online account with us from outside Switzerland, you agree to the terms of this Policy and our Terms of Service, and give your consent to the transfer to and processing of such information in Switzerland. Our company is registered in Bulgaria, so we abide by the Bulgarian laws and we adhere to the GDPR (European General Data Protection Regulation) and any other data protection legislations enforceable in Bulgaria.  
  
**Data Protection Officer**  
  
Even though the only personal data we collect is your Email address, which in our understanding, depending on the specifics of the Email address may not constitute personal information, we have decided to appoint a Data Protection Officer with professional education in the sphere of Informational Technology and Security and expert knowledge in network and data security to further conform with GDPR (European General Data Protection Regulation) and strengthen any case about your data being treated professionally and in line with current law and highest standards.  
  
Anton Belodedenko  
anton \[at\] vpnarea.com  
Vuzrazhdane 27, ap 5  
Varna, Bulgaria,  
9000  

**How To Contact Us**  
  
For questions about this Site or VPNArea, or for more information about how we or our service providers treat your personal information, please contact us at: support \[at\] vpnarea.com  
  
**Changes to this Policy**  
  
We may change this Policy from time to time consistent with applicable privacy laws and principles. If we do so, we will post a new effective date for that Policy and follow obligations about notifying you of such changes.  

© 2022 Offshore Security LTD, all rights reserved
